a cat with a white and black stripe on its face
Gat Siberià Mirant
a lone polar bear is standing in the middle of the water
Tortuga Carei
an elephant walking through a grassy field
Elefant Caminant per la Sabana
a small brown and white animal eating a piece of food
Gos de la Praderia Rosegant
a large brown bear eating a piece of food
Mandril Badallant
a small brown and white striped animal
Lleopard Llepant-se la Pota
a brown and white cat with a green face
Linx Euroasiàtic Amenaçador
a zebra standing on top of a grass covered field
Antílop del Nil Pasturant
a cat standing on a rock near a pond
Llúdriga Euroasiàtica Cridant la seva Parella
a small bird sitting on a branch in a forest
Mico Esquirol Caçant Mosques
a large brown bear standing on top of a rock
Llúdriga de Riu Nedant
a small brown bear standing in the grass
Guepard Juvenil
a zebra walking through a grassy field
Guepard al Masai Mara
a close up of a close up of a close up of a face
Primer Pla d’un Guepard
a zebra standing on top of a lush green field
Zebra a l’Àfrica
a brown and white striped animal standing in the grass
Primer Pla d’un Lleó
a white dog standing in a grassy field
Retrat de Lleó Blanc
elephants are standing on the beach
Grup d’Hipopòtams
a large elephant walking through a dry area
Elefant Africà Prenent un Bany de Fang
two zebras standing in a muddy area next to a body of water
Zebra Bevent Aigua
a large brown animal walking through a grassy area
Dos Llops al Bosc
a herd of zebras grazing in a field
Migració de Zebres i Nyus
giraffes are walking through a field
Una Família de Girafes
a small white and black bird standing in a field
Berrendre a Wyoming
a small brown and white dog standing on a dirt field
Bell Guineu Roja
a brown and white cow standing in a field
Cabirol Europeu
a black dog with a black collar and a black bow
Cadell de Mastí Italià